I really pride myself on being able to see people in their hurt.
I'm really good at that.
And I know that's because I'm an empath, but I'm really good at that.
I didn't feel seen in mine.
And I feel like it's because I didn't know how to show it.
But I also don't feel like I should have to.
I mean, I guess what I'm asking for is for people to read my mind.
And I guess that's not fair either.
I just would have liked to have been checked on.
I would have liked there to have been a more concerted effort at gathering me.
You know, it's like for colored girls.
I was missing something.
Something promised.
A lying on of hands, fingers near the forehead, strong, making me whole.
The holiness of myself released.
I found God in myself and I loved her.
And this is for colored girls who've considered suicide,
but are moving to the ends of their own rainbows.
That's what I wanted.